let quiz = [
    {
        question: "1. What does HTML stand for?",
        answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "Hyper Text Machine Language",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Hyper Text Multiple Language",
            "Hyper Tool Multi Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "2. What does CSS stand for?",
        answer: "Cascading Style Sheet",
        options: [
            "Common Style Sheet",
            "Colorful Style Sheet",
            "Computer Style Sheet",
            "Cascading Style Sheet"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "3. What does SQL stand for?",
        answer: "Structured Query Language",
        options: [
            "Stylish Question Language",
            "Stylesheet Query Language",
            "Statement Question Language",
            "Structured Query Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "4. What does XML stand for?",
        answer: "eXtensible Markup Language",
        options: [
            "eXtensible Markup Language",
            "eXecutable Multiple Language",
            "eXTra Multi-Program Language",
            "eXamine Multiple Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "5. In CSS, choose the correct option to select an element by its id (id='idName')?",
        answer: "#idName { }",
        options: [
            ".idName { }",
            "*idName { }",
            "idname { }",
            "#idName { }"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "6. Select the option to make a list that lists the items with bullets?",
        answer: "Ul",
        options: [
            "List",
            "Ul",
            "Dl",
            "Ol"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "7. Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
        answer: "< script >",
        options: [
            "&lt; script &gt;",
            " &lt; javascript &gt;",
            "&lt; js &gt;",
            "&lt; scripting &gt;"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "8. Where is the correct place to link a JavaScript?",
        answer: "Both the <head> section and the <body> section",
        options: [
            "The &lt;head&gt; section",
            "The &lt;body&gt; section",
            "Both the &lt;head&gt; section and the &lt;body> section",
            "No need to link"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "9. What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'quiz.js'?",
        answer: '< script src="quiz.js">',
        options: [
            '&lt; a href="quiz.js" &gt;',
            '&lt; script href="quiz.js"&gt;',
            '&lt; a src="quiz.js"&gt;',
            '&lt; script src="quiz.js"&gt;'
        ]
    },
    {
        question: '10. How do you write "Hello World" in an alert box?',
        answer: 'alert("Hello World");',
        options: [
            'msg("Hello World");',
            'alertBox("Hello World");',
            'msgBox("Hello World");',
            'alert("Hello World");'
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "11. How do you create a function in JavaScript?",
        answer: "function myFunction()",
        options: [
            "function:myFunction()",
            "function myFunction()",
            "function = myFunction()",
            "function -> myFunction()"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "12. What is the correct way to write a JavaScript array?",
        answer: 'var array = ["HTML", "CSS", "JS"]',
        options: [
            'var array = "HTML", "CSS", "JS"',
            'var array = (1:"HTML", 2:"CSS", 3:"JS")',
            'var array = ["HTML", "CSS", "JS"]',
            'var array = 1:("HTML"), 2:("CSS"), 3:("JS")'
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "13. How do you round the number 7.25, to the nearest integer?",
        answer: "Math.round(7.25)",
        options: [
            "round(7.25)",
            "Math.round(7.25)",
            "md(7.25)",
            "Math.md(7.25)"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: '14. What is the correct JavaScript syntax for opening a new window called "w2" ?',
        answer: 'w2 = window.open("https://www.newtonschool.com")',
        options: [
            'w2 = window.new("https://www.newtonschool.com")',
            'w2 = window.open("https://www.newtonschool.com")',
            'w2 = window.create("https://www.newtonschool.com")',
            'w2 = window.newWindow("https://www.newtonschool.com")'
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "15. Which event occurs when the user clicks on an HTML element?",
        answer: "onclick",
        options: [
            "onchange",
            "onclick",
            "onmouseclick",
            "onmouseover"
        ]
    }
 ]
// console.log(quiz);
// console.log(quiz[4].answer);